en:
  global:
    organization_name: "The Haven Project"
    organization_description:
          "The Haven Project provides direct service to more
          than 200 homeless unaccompanied youth ages 17-24 each
          year in our Drop-in Centers, with referrals to other youth
          serving organizations for hundreds more who don't meet intake
          criteria based on age, homelessness or other factors."
    menu:
      home: "Home"
      newsletter: "Newsletter"
      sign_up: "Sign Up"
      sign_in: "Sign In"
      sign_out: "Sign Out"
      admin: "Admin"
      events: "Events"
      groups: "Groups"
      users: "Users"
      my_profile: "My Profile"
    deleted: "Deleted"
    updated: "Updated"
    new: "New"
    non_message: "Non-Message"
    not_delivered: "Not Delivered"
    delivered: "Delivered"
    not_responded: "Not Responding"
    not_attending: "Not Attending"
    attending: "Attending"
    welcome: "Welcome to <br> %{organization_name}"
    not_found: "Your %{type} was not found. Please try again, and if this persists, contact the administrator."
    error_message: "An error has occurred saving your %{type}. Please contact the administrator."
    invalid_input: "Invalid input. Please try again."
    invalid_action: "This action cannot be completed. Please try another selection or try again later."
    warning: "You must be signed in as a(n) %{type} to view this page!"
  users:
    registrations:
      create_by_admin:
        type_missing: "Creation failed. Please input either email, phone number, or both."
        csv_success: "Users have been created."
        csv_failures: "Users have all failed. Please review your CSV and resubmit. The following rows failed:<br><br>%{rows}"
        csv_success_with_failures: "Users have been created, but there were failures. Please review your CSV and edit the failed rows should you want to create them. The following rows failed:<br><br>%{rows}"
  texts:
    confirmation: "Welcome %{name} to %{organization_name}! Respond CONFIRM to confirm your interest in notifications, STOP to cancel."
    new_event: "New %{type}:\n%{params}%{prompt}"
    updated_event: "%{type} updated:\n%{params}%{prompt}"
    deleted_event: "%{type} deleted:\n%{params}"
    new_prompt: "Respond %{id}Y to confirm your attendance, %{id}N to decline."
    updated_prompt: "If you haven't already, respond %{id}Y to confirm your attendance, %{id}N to decline."
    confirmation_success_response: "Thanks! You are now confirmed!"
    confirmation_failed_response: "You are already confirmed."
    stop_success_response: "You will no longer receive notifications."
    stop_failed_response: "You already do not receive notifications. Please reregister to recieve notifications."
  events:
    new:
      create: "Create event"
      create_prompt: "Please fill out this form to create an event!"
    edit:
      edit: "Edit event"
      edit_prompt: "Please fill out this form to modify and/or publish event!"
    update:
      success: "Your event was successfully modified!"
    create:
      success: "Your event was successfully created!"
    destroy:
      success: "Your event was successfully deleted!"
    attending_success_response: "You are now confirmed!"
    attending_failed_response: "You are already confirmed."
    not_attending_success_response: "You are no longer confirmed."
    not_attending_failed_response: "You are already unconfirmed."
    title: "Title"
    description: "Description"
    when: "When"
    where: "Where"
    type: "Type"
    published: "Published"
  groups:
    new:
      create: "Create group"
      create_prompt: "Please fill out this form to create an group!"
    edit:
      edit: "Edit group"
      edit_prompt: "Please fill out this form to modify and/or publish group!"
    update:
      success: "Your group was successfully modified!"
    create:
      success: "Your group was successfully created!"
    destroy:
      success: "Your group was successfully deleted!"
    name: "Name"
  devise:
    registrations:
      new:
        sign_up: "Sign Up"
        sign_up_prompt: "Please fill out this form to create an account!"
      new_by_admin:
        form: "Create user via form"
        form_prompt: "Please fill out this form to create an account!"
        csv: "Create user via CSV"
        csv_prompt: "Click here for a user CSV template!"
    sessions:
      new:
        login: "Login"
        login_prompt: "Please login below using your username, email, or phone number."
